https://chenghsin.com/new/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
Who we are?
Our website address is: https://chenghsin.com/new. (Herin referred to as “We” “Us” “Cheng Hsin” “This Site”)
We are a company in service of the growth of consciousness and skill. We are located in Texas, USA. Our mailing address is:
PO Box 63080
Pipe Cree, TX
78063
What personal data we collect and why we collect it?
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
We use contact forms from MailChimp and Google Forms.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
We use Google Analytics to track website page visits, duration, etc.. We do not track mouse movements.
Who we share your data with?
We do not sell your information to third party sites. We use some third party sites to store personal information including:
Paypal
Woocommerce
Maichimp
Google Forms
Google Sheets
How long we retain your data?
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data?
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data?
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
We keep your contact information secure and for private use only.
Additional information
How we protect your data?
We use SSL encryption from our hosting service.
We utilize secure third party sites and rely on their protective measures to keep your information secure.
What data breach procedures we have in place?
The procedures supplied by wordpress.org, paypal, and mailchimp as well as any other third party site we choose.
What third parties we receive data from?
Mail Chimp
Google Analytics
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data?
None.
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time so visitors are encouraged to review this policy from time to time. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.
Copyright 2019 Cheng Hsin all rights reserved
